niftylivecharts.com 2013-10-10

# Privacy Policy - niftyLiveCharts.com

Join BankNifty Package for 3 Months @ Rs 14,200 and Get Guaranteed Profit of 60%. Limited time offer. Call 9899555993 to know more

By Accessing this site you agree to our Terms & conditions and Disclaimer Copyright © 2008 - 2015 NiftyLivecharts.com    
Cancellation/Refund |  Privacy Policy | Terms & condition | Disclaimer  
Office Address : 227 - 228 RG MALL Sector 9 Rohini New Delhi 110085

Our Privacy Policy ( niftyLiveCharts.com)  
NiftyLiveCharts.com Advisory Services (“NiftyLiveCharts.com”) is committed to safeguard our clients and subscribers privacy online. Our Privacy policy is explained below. we deserve the rights to change the Policy periodically or whenever needed.

1\. Information gathered via website  
we gathers two types of information about our users.  
(a) Personal information that individual users provide through registration, and  
(b) tracking information, which is automatically collected about every visitor.

2\. Subscriptions  
Any subscriber is not entitled to cancel his membership, and claim back his subscription. His membership automatically cancelled, once he does not renew his subscription next month.  
Subscription fee once paid is non-refundable due to the nature of our business.

3\. Personal Information  
Personal information is gathered for several ways.   
Like Registration Forms , Free Trial Forms and Google Groups.  
Wherever we collect personal information, we make an effort to include a link to our Privacy Policy on that page.

4\. Use  
NiftyLiveCharts.com uses information obtained from its users to enhance their experience on the website.  
We do not rent or sell any personal information about our subscribers or other users. As a general rule, we will not disclose any personal information to any third parties. So your information is safe with us.

NiftyLiveCharts.com may disclose account or personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating NiftyLiveCharts.com’s Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) NiftyLiveCharts.com rights or property, other NiftyLiveCharts.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. NiftyLiveCharts.com may disclose or access account or personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

5\. Incorrect Information  
The accuracy of your personal information is important to us. If you are a paid subscriber and have a concern about your personal or account information maintained at NiftyLiveCharts.com, or want to correct, update, or confirm your information, please send us an email at info [at] niftylivecharts [dot] com. We will be happy to review and update your information with our records.

6\. Security  
Your subscriber account information and your profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personal information. You may correct your personal information as explained in Section 5.  
We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. NiftyLiveCharts.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or an Internet cafe.  
Because the nature of the Service provided on NiftyLiveCharts.com, has users all over the world, and takes adequate steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, NiftyLiveCharts.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account or personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

**Get 60% Assured Return in 3 Months in BankNifty Tips. Limited time offer. Call 9899555993 - 01147010987 to know more.**
